This was halloween
and this is me dressed up as
a future dentist.
So as a first grader, I just wrote,
I know learning is important
because I wanted to help
my dad and let my dad be rich.
What drew me to dentistry,
my dad had his
wisdom teeth extracted.
A couple days later, something was wrong.
He suffered a pretty bad infection
that had actually spread.
He actually became paralyzed
for three months.
That piqued my interest in dentistry.
2015 is when I had the opportunity
to start my own practice in this space right here.
I had no business knowledge, no training,
we were just kind of stepping over one another
and just bursting at the seams.
And that's when I started dreaming a little bit bigger.
And that gave me the confidence to
take that leap of faith to expand.
Hi, good to see you.
Staff: Thank you
Thank you
Take a seat here.
Patient: I’m going to tell you I've been flossing every day,
Patient: but I haven't.
The cornerstone of our practice is about
the relationship that we build with the patients.
We really wanted to make sure they just feel at home.
Yeah, I met my wife in dental school.
It was never our plan to practice together.
But after some time, it just made sense having
Grace's pediatric practice on the first floor
and my general practice upstairs.
Before Lassie, Grace's purse and my backpack
would just be filled with papers,
we'd just be drowning in a sea of paperwork.
After seeing a patient, insurance companies would
mail us a paper check four to five weeks later.
I was dreading having to post and manually enter
hundreds of patients
and thousands of procedure codes
After you start staring at that piece of paper for hours,
you would almost become like delirious.
Lassie has been a game changer for us.
Personally, it saves over a hundred hours
of manual data entry time and admin time a month.
It's really accelerated cash flow and now
in less than a week, the money is
directly deposited into my bank account.
And so ...es us up to really focus on patient experience,
but also growth opportunities.
Because of Lassie, it's created a margin of time
for my family and for me personally.
And so that's allowed me to coach
my kids' sports teams
and to attend their practices and games.
You know, I think early in my career,
success was more about individual achievement.
It was ... material maybe, about career, about wealth.
And I realized success is about service.
It's about relationships. It's about family.
So that's what success means to me.